dcrazed.net 2019-08-10

# Privacy Policy - DesignSeer

_This is our updated Privacy Policy which goes into effect on May 25, 2018._

###  Who we are

Our website address is: https://designseer.com.

This privacy policy describes how DesignSeer.com uses and protects any information that you give us. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. If you provide us with personal information through DesignSeer.com, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

### What Personal Data We Collect And Why We Collect It

 **Use of personal information**

We use the information you provide to register for an account, receive newsletters, write comments, use certain other services, or participate in our support forums.

We will not sell or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

We would like to send you email marketing communication which may be of interest to you from time to time. If you have consented to marketing, you may opt out later.

You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email.

### Access to data

You have the right to request a copy of the information we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all your personal information, please follow the instructions at the end of this policy.

DesignSeer.com user accounts can be edited by following these steps:  
1) Visit <https://designseer.com/wp-login.php>, and then enter your username and password.  
2) You will be redirected to https://profiles.designseer.com/your_username.  
3) Click the “Edit” link next to your username.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, DesignSeer.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. DesignSeer.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how DesignSeer.com’s visitors use its website. From time to time, DesignSeer.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

DesignSeer.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. DesignSeer.com does not use IP addresses to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Aggregated Statistics

DesignSeer.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, DesignSeer.com may monitor the most popular pages on any competitor site or use spam screened by the Antispam Bee service to help identify spam. DesignSeer.com may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, DesignSeer.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our website. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Google also collects Demographics and interests data so that our website may provide you with the best user experience.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

### Third Party Links

Our website may contain links to other websites provided by third parties, not under our control. When following a link and providing information to a 3rd-party website, please be aware that we are not responsible for the data provided to that third party. This privacy policy only applies to the websites listed at the beginning of this document, so when you visit other websites, even when you click on a link posted on DesignSeer.com, you should read their own privacy policies.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to save your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Ads

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by DesignSeer.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact / Subscription Forms

Customers that email us, or use any of the contact forms on our websites, will have their email address, IP address, and any data provided in the contact form or body of the email stored in G Suite archives and in our third-party service provider, Mailchimp. We use email marketing to communicate with customers and potential customers from time to time. All email lists and campaigns are “opt-in” meaning we will not send you these sorts of emails unless you indicated that you wish to receive them during signup or other interactions on our website. All marketing emails sent by us will include an unsubscribe link in the footer of the email. Emails sent to you may also include standard tracking, including open and click activities.

### Registered Users

Certain visitors to DesignSeer.com choose to interact with DesignSeer.com in ways that require DesignSeer.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that DesignSeer.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who use our forums to provide a username and email address.

In each case, DesignSeer.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with DesignSeer.com. DesignSeer.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Who We Share Your Data With

DesignSeer.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of project administrators, employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on DesignSeer.com’s behalf or to provide services available through DesignSeer.com, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using DesignSeer.com, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

DesignSeer.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to project administrators, employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, DesignSeer.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, if you give permission to have your information shared, or when DesignSeer.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of DesignSeer.com, third parties, or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of a DesignSeer.com website and have supplied your email address, DesignSeer.com may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with DesignSeer.com and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum.

If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. DesignSeer.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

### How We Protect Your Data

The security and reliability of our service is our number one priority. We invest heavily in the training of our staff and our infrastructure to ensure that best practices are followed in everything that we do.

See [wordpress.org/about/security](http://wordpress.org/about/security) for details on the security of the WordPress core itself.

  * Prevention is best when it comes to security, and as a first step, we follow all WordPress Code Standards in the plugins that we build and use.
  * In addition, we have an extensive internal review and Quality Assurance process in place specifically to prevent potential security vulnerabilities in our plugins and services.
  * At DesignSeer.com we make sure to limit access to customer data by authors, registered users.
  * We only use third-party services, such as Fastcomet, Stackpath, Ahrefs, Semrush that are fully vetted and adhere to the highest levels of privacy and security practices.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, DesignSeer.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at DesignSeer.com’s sole discretion. DesignSeer.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Contact

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you by emailing mail@designseer.com.
